{
    "subject": "resource/United_States",
    "predicate": "property/cctld",
    "object": "resource/.us",
    "human_readable": "The country code top-level domain of United States is .us.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.979720413684845,
            "question": "What is the country code top-level domain of the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7836290001869202,
            "question": "What does the top-level domain .us signify?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5958268642425537,
            "question": "How do you represent the United States online using a top-level domain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4361908733844757,
            "question": "Which country's web addresses use the extension .us?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3664318323135376,
            "question": "If you wanted to visit a website from the United States, what would be its domain extension?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3648597300052643,
            "question": "What does '.us' stand for in internet domain names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35986724495887756,
            "question": "Which country's internet addresses end in .us?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2211778312921524,
            "question": "Is .us a valid internet address for websites from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14764457941055298,
            "question": "Give an example of a website address from the United States."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09602948278188705,
            "question": "What is the short form used to denote the United States on the internet?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The country code top-level domain of United States is .us.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8066_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Give an example of a website address from the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8066_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is .us a valid internet address for websites from the United States?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8066_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which country's internet addresses end in .us?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8066_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8066_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8066_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8066_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8066_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8066_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8066_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8066_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8066_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8066_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8066_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response indicates that the statement \"The country code top-level domain of United States is .us\" is supported by the provided context information. The documents mention \".us\" as the official top-level domain (TLD) of the United States, a country-code top-level domain for the United States, and the very first ccTLD dating back to 1985."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents support the statement that the country-code top-level domain (ccTLD) for the United States is \".us\". Multiple sources within the context indicate this, such as direct definitions and descriptions of what a .us domain signifies and its restricted availability to U.S. entities or citizens."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}